Thank you so much for stepping away from
the party. We're so excited to have you.
Um on this call is our local media. So
we're just going to go ahead and get
started and ask you a couple questions
and then you can get back to
celebrating.
>> For sure.
>> Okay, cool. Let's go ahead and get
started with uh Pete Sweeney.
>> I said I'll have a second one.
Congratulations uh Mason. Uh just
curious how much contact you had with
the Chiefs and just any awareness of you
know maybe that this was actually coming
for Kansas City. Yeah, I didn't expect
this. You know, I had a former meeting
with them. Uh I know Ethan DS, another U
alumni that uh is at the Chiefs, but
yeah, I wouldn't necessarily I didn't I
didn't know who it was once the second
round started.
>> And it seemed like in your college
career, you had a a knack for closing
games. Uh it seems like that's a special
trait of yours. Where do you think that
ability comes from? um just as you as
you've gone on in your football career.
>> Yeah, it's the relentlessness that
people talk about. It's not about
talking about is going to doing it. So,
we talk about relentlessness all day and
yeah, it gets to a point where you know,
you know what's going to come, the the
fans know what's going to come. Mom and
the stands know what's going to come.
So, it's like the anticipation to go and
and have the the the
endurance to still play fast at the end
of the the the game is that's where it
comes from. And it's like we do all this
conditioning, so might as well use it, I
guess. You know what I mean?
>> Well, we'll go next to Sam McDow.
>> Hey, Mason. What's up, man? Um, what was
your reaction to getting picked?
>> Yeah, I was surprised. I I was I was
excited. Um, there's a lot of noise, but
that was the main three.
>> And I just wonder if you could describe
your style, just h how you get after the
quarterback, how you win most.
I win most. It's all about um just
having there relentlessness. Uh
relentlessness
not yeah relentless relentless.
>> We'll go next to Todd Lebo.
>> Hey uh R Mason. Couple things. Did they
did they talk to you about like position
stuff when they when they talked to you
because kind of a tweener sized uh what
what sort of things have they told you
when they talked to you tonight and when
you're meeting with them before? How
would you fit in here?
>> We didn't necessarily go into depth
about that at the time. So, I couldn't
tell you an answer.
>> And then uh I know you've talked about
this before. Can you tell us the story
of your name? uh how it's just the
letter R and and kind of how that all
thing came about.
>> Yeah, my mom all all the males almost
every male in her side of family starts
with an R. She wanted to keep the R
going. She wanted to leave like the R,
you know, continuence to my uncle, her
brother that's going to eventually had a
son because I was the firstborn son and
her siblings. So, she like Mason, you
know, capital R space capital Mason. So,
she wanted to keep the R going but not
be a R name like Richard Raymond.
Okay, we'll go next to Nick Jacobs.
>> And Sydney, I'll have a follow-up if I
can, please. Uh, Arm Mason, for you,
when did you fall in love with the game
of football that you decided this is
what you wanted to reach at the highest
peak for?
>> Yeah, I knew little league
once I started football like 9 years
old, that was going to be, you know,
what I wanted to do. And it didn't
really like come into fruition till like
sophomore year of high school. So, I
knew where I could work hard enough to
be in this position.
>> And then when you're out there on the
football field, what is it that you're
kind of wanting to put on tape for the
offensive lineman to make them fearful
when they're going against you that
week?
>> Yeah, just be if I could put on tape or
if I'm um unpredictable, that's where it
gets to be, you know, field day for a
defensive end. Then when a tacker
doesn't know what you're necessarily
going to do, that's when it becomes
good.
>> We'll go next to Nate Taylor.
>> Hello, R. Congratulations. Um, I have
two questions as well. My first is what
excites you most about joining the
Chiefs and the conversations you had
with them before tonight.
>> Yeah, the traditions, the the
winning a winning program, what they how
they do it, what they do. I'm excited to
to to to know the ins and out of what
they actually do because you know you've
been on the outside of it. You don't
necessarily know Ethan downs on the
inside but it's different when you
experience it for your own,
>> right? And I think where do you feel
like you can get better as a player?
Like what do you want to show in terms
of improvement from college to the NFL?
>> Yeah, consistency. Consistent on the
edge, consistent send the edge,
consistent rushing passer, consistent
getting the quarterback on the ground.
If I could do that consistently, I think
that's where I could be better.
>> We just have one more with Matt Derek.
Go ahead, Matt.
>> Hey, R Mason. Is that how you'd like to
be preferred? How do you like for people
to address you?
>> Yeah, Arm Mason or Mace. Either one.
>> Good to know. Thank you. Um, it looks
like you had a pretty good party there
tonight. Who's all celebrating with you
and who's there with you tonight?
>> Yeah, fam. church fan, uh, relatives,
any anybody that's close to me you can
think of.
>> And, you know, like like some of the
guys mentioned earlier, you know, you
are a bit different size for this
position in Kansas City. Are there any
players around the league that that you
particularly watch and model your
pattern your game after?
>> Yep. Nonito. That's that's the number
one the one of the reasons why I went to
Oklahoma. So, that was a big thing.
Have you met him? And were you recruited
by him? I mean, any any connections
there?
>> No, I I wasn't recruited by him because
he he was going to the league around
this time when I was just coming to be a
freshman and he he was a part of the
leaking staff, so he didn't necessarily
know BV. Uh but yeah, I definitely
talked to him. My first time ever
meeting him was around this time last
year uh for their spring game. And yeah,
I've been in contact texting about
different things to get better.
Thank you.
>> Okay, Armes, that's all we have for you.
Go back to go back to your party and
celebrate. Appreciate it.